<Publish>
  <ModId Value="75826" />
  <DisplayName Value="Plop the Growables" />
  <ShortDescription Value="Stops growable buildings being condemned if they're outside the correct (or any) zone." />
  <LongDescription>## Plop the Growables
- **Disables growable building zone checks**
- **Disable building level changes for user-selected individual buildings**
- Optionally **disable building level changes for ALL buildings**

### Disables growable building zone checks
This means that you can place them anywhere (using the dev UI) - on zoning, off zoning, partially on zoning, on incorrect zoning, wherever - and they won't despawn.

This allows the manual placement of growable buildings directly, without needing any workarounds such as making them signature buildings.

Note that buildings will still require road access (including for water/sewerage/electricity) to function properly, but they don't have to be perfectly aligned with the road.

### Disable level changes for individual buildings
This mod adds a 'lock building level' toggle to the building info panel for growable buildings.  Select this toggle to keep that building at the same level.

Note that builing level-up progress within the current level will still show on the building's level up progress panel, but it will never reach the level required to upgrade to the next level.

### Disable ALL building level changes (optional)
This can be toggled in the mod's options panel (the default is **off**).  When this is enabled all growable buildings will keep their current level, ensuring that they also keep their appearance.

Note that builing level-up progress within the current level will still show on the building's level up progress panel, but it will never reach the level required to upgrade to the next level.

## How to select and place growable buildings
This mod doesn't have its own UI - instead, use TDW's **Find It** mod to select and place growable buildings (or use the game's developer mode).

## Meta
### Translations
This mod supports localization. Please help out with translating this mod into different languages via the CrowdIn site at crowdin.com/project/plop-the-growables.

### Modders
Modders (and aspiring modders!), as always I'm available and happy to chat about what I've done and answer any questions, and also about how you can implement anything that I've done for your own mods. Come grab me on the Cities: Skylines Modding Discord!

### Credits
Thanks to TPB, the creator of the original Plop the Growables mod for Cities: Skylines 1, which inspired the idea of this one.</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/IgnoreZoning.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/LockBuilding.jpg" />
  <Tag Value="" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/plop-the-growables.1644731/" />
  <ModVersion Value="0.3" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
  <Dependency Id="77240" DisplayName="Find It" />
  <Dependency Id="74417" DisplayName="Unified Icon Library" Version="1.0.1" />
  <ChangeLog>- Add level locking for individual buildings.</ChangeLog>
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/algernon-A/PlopTheGrowables" />
  <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
  <ExternalLink Type="ko-fi" Url="https://ko-fi.com/algernon" />
</Publish>